Now, this one's very nice.
Now, 这个非常不错
What's it made of?
它是用什么做成的?
It's made of leather.
用皮做成的.
But leather is too heavy for me.
但是皮革太重了对我来说.
And it's too expensive.
而且它太昂贵了.
How about this one? This isn't heavy.
这个如何? 这个不太重.
This is plastic.
这是塑料的.
It's lighter, but it's too light.
这个更轻一些, 但是太轻了.
It can't take the battering.
它无法承受碰撞(battering)
And look. it's too small.
And look, 它太小了.
Oh.
Now this. This is a new design.
现在(看)这个. 这是一个新的设计.
It's a good size.
它是一个好的尺寸.
24 inches by 14 inches by 10 inches.
24英寸 * 14英寸 * 10英寸.
It's made of strong nylon.
它是又强尼龙做成的.
It's light, but not too light.
它是轻的. 但是不会太轻.
How much does it weigh?
它有多重?
Not more than five pounds.
不超过5磅
It's small enough to go under a seat on a plane,
它小到足以放到座椅下边 在飞机上.
yet big enough to carry a suit, a few shirts...and a computer notebook.
但大到足以携带一件西装, 几件衬衫,和一个笔记本电脑
Wow.
It's got a handle. It's got wheels.
它有一个把手. 它有轮子.
How much does it cost? Is it expensive?
多少钱? 它贵吗?
Not too expensive. $120.
不太贵. 120美元.
So you recommend this one?
所以你推荐这一款?
Recommend it? I have one just like it!
推荐它? 我有一个和它一模一样的!